[{"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 5, "question": "Would you really?", "qSentId": 4}, {"answer": "I'm doing good.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "Ryan, how are you?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "Yes, I'm happy.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 51, "question": "Are you happy?", "qSentId": 50}, {"answer": "Yes, I'd say so.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "Drinking competitions, I mean?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "I've been asked this question before.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "Who gets more women?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "I think it's a tossup.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 81, "question": "It's you, isn't it?", "qSentId": 80}, {"answer": "I'm sure it's --", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "It's you, isn't it?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "That would have to be a family-loving person that could stand having a large family, and crazy family at that.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "Who would be the right kind of woman for your boy?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "She meant that I go on dates.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "What does she mean by that?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "Right now, Blake Lively.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "Who would you take right now?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "Would you really?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": "No, never met her.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "Have you met her?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "I'd be like, hi.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "If she's watching this, and she probably is, what would you say to her?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "She's dating Ryan Reynolds who I think he's overrated.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "Do you want to go to an island with me?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "A lot of money.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "How much is that worth?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 162, "question": "You like your bling, do you?", "qSentId": 161}, {"answer": "You know what, it's hard to choose from a different country, because there's so many that are outstanding.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "Did you wake up and think Chinese -- are they the big rivals now?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "You know, he did come up and say congrats.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "Did you expect Michael Phelps to come and congratulate you, or did you understand in that moment he was like, you're the last guy he wants to talk to?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "Not in the pool.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "Not in the pool, right?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "It takes a lot, a lot of early-morning practices, and going into a freezing cold pool.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 205, "question": "What kind of dedication does it take to be a gold medal winner at the Olympic Games?", "qSentId": 204}, {"answer": "That, this right here.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "What is in your head?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "Chills.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 218, "question": "What is going through your mind?", "qSentId": 217}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "Do you feel like you are swimming for America?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "Greatest feeling in your life when you win a gold?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "After this interview I'm going to go over there and get a Big Mac.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "Are you just so fit now you can go to the huge McDonald's over there, the world's biggest McDonald's, gorge yourself on Big Macs for an hour?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "Can you eat what you like, seriously?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "Do you feel like you're a New Yorker still?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "I can't do the cold that much.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "What do you feel?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "Eleven.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "You moved to Florida, what, you were 8 years old you said?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "I tried to steer him as being an honest, fun-loving, caring individual.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "When he was a young guy, what kind of young boy did you try to steer him toward being as a man?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "No, never, never.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "Did he ever beat you, or did you say, you know what, when you beat me for real?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "That's a hard question to answer.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "As a parent, which is the more extreme?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "When I was on the podium, the national anthem was being raised and they showed the JumboTron.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "Was when?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "I do, I love it.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "You love this, don't you?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "I love it.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "Do you like it?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "You know, I guess it's part of my personality.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 387, "question": "What does it say about you when you put this in your mouth?", "qSentId": 386}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "Do you read this?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "I mean --", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 399, "question": "Are you amused or bemused by the fact you have a guy pretending to be you tweeting to the world?", "qSentId": 398}, {"answer": "I'm doing good.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "Veronica, how are you?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "Very well.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "I don't know what the future holds.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "You're the woman who's going to break all American hearts by beating Allyson Felix, aren't you?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "Yes, indeed, Trelawny.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "It's actually where Usain Bolt comes from as well, isn't it?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "There's a lot of factors.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 438, "question": "Why are you all being created in this tiny little part of Jamaica?", "qSentId": 437}, {"answer": "I do enjoy eating yam.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "Are you a big yam eater?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "I imagine it was very competitive when you were young, right?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "You used to run bare foot, right?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "AMPBELL-BROWN: I do.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "Did you beat the boys?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "I'm calm.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "When you're getting down there and you're the favorite, the pressure is on, what are you feeling in that moment?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "Jamaica and the U.S. have a very rich tradition in the sprint and I enjoy competing.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "And you're able to hold off America and you're able to hold off America and all these American sprinters when it's 350 times as big as Jamaica?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "No, no, I haven't.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 492, "question": "Do you ever quietly get it on when you're back in Chalorny?", "qSentId": 491}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "Do you reckon you could take him?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "AMPBELL-BROWN: He's a very talented athlete.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "Is he a real good guy in real life?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "I did yesterday.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "You've been seeing the swimming event?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "He's gorgeous.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "Are you keen on him?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "A lot.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "How many times are you plan on watching the swimming this week?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "I love gymnastics.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 540, "question": "What are your other favorite sports?", "qSentId": 539}, {"answer": "Not necessarily playing sports.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "Are you a sporty girl?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, the thing is, I think when you are preparing to could something like that, I think it should really be up to you.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 549, "question": "What did you think of that?", "qSentId": 548}, {"answer": "Of course, I would sing it.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 561, "question": "You would sing it, wouldn't you?", "qSentId": 560}, {"answer": "I think it's actually really exciting, you know, because it's like an all-star cast.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "What do you think of it?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "The opening ceremony was pretty spectacular, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "Honestly, it was the queen.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 580, "question": "What was your favorite part?", "qSentId": 579}, {"answer": "Well, it's a campaign for sort of getting the country behind the team, as the host nation.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 594, "question": "What does that mean?", "qSentId": 593}, {"answer": "I'm off now to South Africa at the end of the week, Taiwan, Japan, China, and I'm going to be back in the United States in November and December.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 603, "question": "Where are you going on tour next?", "qSentId": 602}, {"answer": "It's lovely.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 607, "question": "How are you coping with your new-found fame in America?", "qSentId": 606}, {"answer": "I'm very well.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "Alfie Boe, how are you doing?", "qSentId": 622}, {"answer": "Well, it's great for me because I know they've all been listening to the actual anthem.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "Bradley Wiggins and his sideburns, everything else, what does it feel like to be a Brit right now?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "I've polished a lot of cars in my life so I try to avoid it.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 640, "question": "Do you still work on cars?", "qSentId": 639}, {"answer": "For me personally, I'm proud to be British.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 643, "question": "When you look at the Olympic spirit, what does it mean to you?", "qSentId": 642}, {"answer": "We had a house there a while back.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 657, "question": "Do you go there much?", "qSentId": 656}, {"answer": "I sometimes let my frustration run away with me when I see opera houses or the opera establishment telling artists what they can and can't do, saying what is an opera singer, what classical music is and how it should be sacred and kept behind locked doors and things like that.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 667, "question": "What do you do that's so bad?", "qSentId": 666}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 678, "question": "Let's get to your real hero, it's Bruce Springsteen?", "qSentId": 677}, {"answer": "There are two American artists that I would love to work with, Bruce Springsteen and Elmo.", "docId": "120803pmt", "aSentId": 680, "question": "It's your dream to do a duet with the boss?", "qSentId": 679}]